Nice work!
可以呀姐
Renji Hospital is a big client.
仁济医院可是大单位
Bank of Xinfa
之前代发工资那边
had their payroll for ages,
一直被信发银行占着
and you managed to steal it from them.
生抢过来了姐
Impressive!
牛
I'm telling you,
我跟你说啊
if a client can be stolen,
能抢过来的客户呢
they're never
那就不是
really loyal to the other bank.
属于他们的客户
And
还有
once a client is with me,
能到姐手里的客户
they won't leave.
就不会让他再出去
So confident!
霸气
Congrats, Jing.
恭喜静姐
Congrats, Ms. Rao.
恭喜啊饶经理
It's really a case
真的是旱的旱死
of the rich getting richer.
涝的涝死
Your year-end bonus is probably
你的年终奖
more than all of ours combined.
估计比咱加起来都多吧
As for me,
我就惨喽
I'm being targeted by our leader,
被上司针对
and I still have
手里头还有一笔
a bad loan to deal with.
没处理掉的不良贷款
I was hoping for a raise
本来还指望着年底
at the end of the year
能调个薪
for some extra pocket money.
多几块零花钱
But... Xiaoning,
小涂
no luck at all.
没戏了
Speaking of the bad loan,
说到你那个不良贷款
how's it going?
怎么样了
Waiting to deal with the collateral.
等着处理抵押物呗
Wasn't a third-party
不是增加了
guarantee added?
第三方企业担保吗
They don't wanna sell the collateral?
他们不着急卖抵押物啊
A commercial building in a remote area...
偏远郊区的商办楼
Who would buy it?
谁会拍 谁会拍
What do you say?
谁会拍
Once it fails
流拍一次
to sell at auction,
抵押物的价值
the value drops.
就要打个折
30,000,000 yuan in bad loans...
三千万的不良贷款
I'm doomed.
完了 完了
I just hope
我现在就希望
some kind soul
能出现一个善良的人
will save me.
拯救我
God bless.
保佑 保佑
Ms. Rao,
饶经理
Mr. Zhao,
赵经理
let's have
今天晚上辛苦一下
dinner tonight.
跟我去吃个饭
No problem.
没问题
Sorry, Mr. Ji,
不好意思啊纪总
tonight...
我晚上
Xiaoning,
小涂
you join us too.
你晚上也一起
Afterwards, you can drive us.
结束以后帮我们开个车
Okay.
好
Thanks.
辛苦
Aren't you coming?
不去啊
Mr. Ji is too stingy.
这纪总也太寒酸了吧
Inviting clients to dinner,
怎么说都是请客户吃饭
and he didn't choose
不选一家
a classy Western restaurant
环境优雅的西餐
or at least
也得找一家
a decent private kitchen.
品质不错的私房菜吧
You're usually tight-fisted,
平时抠抠搜搜的赵经理
suddenly become
怎么人家
generous when someone else
别人请吃饭的时候
is footing the bill.
你就突然大方起来了
No matter who the guest is,
那不管请的是谁
clients need
客户都需要
to feel valued.
有被重视的感觉
Is this place
这地儿
up to the mark?
那上得了台面吗
I think it's fine.
我觉得还行啊
Mr. Ji must have
纪总 选这儿
his reasons for choosing it.
应该有他的道理吧
Reasons?
道理
The only reason
道理就是
is that he's from Compliance Dept,
他是内控合规出身
always putting on airs.
还端着清高的架子
But fine,
不过正好
I'll take this opportunity to see
今儿我好好学习一下
how this business outsider
他这个业务门外汉
talks about business.
怎么聊业务
Isn't that Mr. Jiang
那不是科技园区的
from the Tech Park?
姜总吗
I thought he never socialized.
他不是从来不应酬吗
So,
所以呀
you should observe and learn today.
你今天就好好学学吧
Yuheng,
纪师弟呀
you picked a great place
你选的这个吃饭的馆子
for dinner.
是真好
The environment
环境是
is elegant and simple,
大方简约
and the dishes
菜品呢
are affordable and tasty.
实惠好吃
Your down-to-earth
像你这种
and unpretentious work attitude
踏踏实实
is something everyone
不奢华的工作态度
should learn from.
值得大家学习
As long as you're satisfied.
只要您满意就好
I am.
满意
Mr. Jiang,
姜总
I'd like to introduce myself.
我再跟您自我介绍一下
I'm Rao Jing,
饶静
a senior client manager.
高级客户经理
Let me toast to you.
我再敬您一杯
Cheers.
来
A good leader can make a good team.
强将手下无弱兵啊
One more, please.
我再给您倒一杯
Mr. Jiang,
姜总
please
我再
allow me to introduce myself.
自我介绍一下
I'm Zhao Fanggang,
我是代瑞的
a senior client manager
高级客户经理
at Dairui.
赵方刚
I wanna propose a toast
我先敬您一杯
to you,
再敬
and Mr. Ji.
我们纪总
He's so kind for inviting us,
感谢纪总邀请我们来
so we have
才能有幸
the honor of meeting you.
一睹姜总的风采呀
I'll down my drink.
那我干了
You can drink at your pace.
您随意
You flatter me.
过奖 过奖
Xiaoning.
小涂
You still have high alcohol tolerance.
师哥酒量还是这么好
Xiaoning is our assistant
小涂是我们
on the business side.
业务端的助理
She's driving today,
她今天开车
so we won't let her drink.
就不让她喝了
Put it down.
放下 放下 放下
Actually,
其实我们
we don't encourage
不搞这个
forced drinking at the table.
酒桌上劝酒这一个
Alcohol
能喝的喝两杯
or juice,
不能喝的
as you like.
这边有果汁
I will
那我
toast you with tea.
以茶代酒敬您
It's an honor to meet you.
很荣幸能够认识您
I'll do the same.
我也
Nice
这个
to meet you.
以茶代酒了
Here,
来师哥
try these dishes.
尝尝这几个菜
No matter how busy work is,
这工作再忙呀
health comes first.
身体还是最主要的
Indeed.
是啊
I heard that
我是听说
you're responsible not only for planning,
您不仅现在要负责规划
but for
这整个园区的
attracting investment
招商引资的重担
for the entire park.
都压您身上了
Did your teacher tell you that?
老赵告诉你的吧
Yes.
是
Honestly,
说实话
I have a headache about this.
想到这个我就头疼
Especially about
头疼那几个
suitable office spaces
大型制造企业
for those large
还找不到合适的
manufacturing companies, right?
办公地点吧
How well-informed you are!
消息很灵通啊
You even know about this.
这件事你都知道
To be frank,
不瞒您说呀
Mr. Zhao has
我们赵经理那儿
two amazing
确实是有两栋
commercial buildings,
非常合适的商办楼
and we can offer them
我们可以免费
to you for free.
提供给你们使用
This sounds
小师弟啊
like a
这可是笔
losing deal.
赔本买卖啊
Besides,
不仅如此
we can also solve
我们还可以
the settlement issues for
为整个园区的小企业
small enterprises in the Park.
解决落户的难题
But I have to
前提是
hand over the loan business
我要把园区企业的
of those enterprises
贷款业务
to Dairui, right?
交给你们代瑞来做是吧
Exactly.
没错
Given the scale
不瞒你说
of the Park,
以我园区的体量来说
it's indeed a big piece of cake,
这可是块大蛋糕
and
而且
several banks
这段日子
have contacted me
已经有好几家银行
recently.
联系过我
But I believe,
不过我相信
you also know that
师哥您一定也清楚
large companies look at the big picture,
大的企业看的是宏观
while small ones
小企业需要的
need practical and hands-on services.
是落地实操性强的服务
In terms of
如果从整体的
overall strength,
硬实力上来讲
Dairui might not
我们代瑞
compare to big banks,
或许比不上其他的大行
but it has absolute advantages
但是真刀真枪的实操
in real-world operations.
我们是绝对的优势
That's right.
没错姜总
Mr. Ji hit the nail on the head.
纪总说得对
We previously provided similar
而且之前我们给
financial services to the investment
桐县的招商办是提供过
promotion office in Tong County,
类似的金融服务的
so we've already
所以呢 我们已经
developed a highly
总结出来了一套
efficient process.
非常高效的流程
Our cooperation can promote
咱要是合作顺畅了
the landing
以后
of investment industries.
招商产业落地
It can also solve problems
我们未来还能为
for small businesses in the future.
其他的小企业排忧解难
A win-win-win.
三赢啊
Mr. Jiang,
姜总
a toast to you.
我敬您一个
Wait a moment.
稍等一下
I didn't expect you young people
没想到你们这些年轻人
to be so insightful
看问题很透彻
and forward-thinking.
而且目光也很长远
Alright,
好
come to my office another day.
改天到我公司细聊
Sure,
师哥
looking forward to our cooperation.
合作愉快啊
- Cheers. - Cheers.
来
Cheers.
来 来
To a bright future.
合作愉快
To be honest,
其实平时吧
I get drunk easily,
我也是一喝就多
but we're having
主要是今天咱们
too much fun today.
聊得太高兴了
Mr. Jiang,
这样 姜总
you drink this much,
您就这一点
and I'll drink a whole glass.
我一杯
I'll drink first
我干了
to show my respect.
我先干为敬
I'll have this drink
这杯酒
with Mr. Jiang.
我跟姜总喝
Cheers.
敬您
Mr. Zhao is also
我们赵经理
kinda drinker.
也挺能喝的
Cool.
来 赵经理
Come here, Mr. Zhao.
过来 过来 过来
Mr. Jiang,
姜总
your phone's ringing.
您电话好像响了
Okay.
好
I'm here.
我在啊
Hello?
喂
Yes,
对呀
Zhongshan Road.
中山路这儿
I'll send you the location.
我发你定位
Ji Yuheng?
纪昱恒
are you alright?
没事吧
I'm fine.
我没事
Okay.
好
My car's here.
我车到了
All right,
行
I'll see you off.
那我送您
I...
我
suddenly realized
突然想起来
that something hasn't been confirmed.
还有件事没有确定呢
What is it?
您说
The free use of the
你刚才说的这个
commercial buildings you mentioned,
免费使用商办楼啊
are there any conditions?
是不是也有条件
Yes,
是
the loan amount
贷款额度
must meet our requirements.
还得按照我们的要求来
Based on
如果说按照
the auction standards,
流拍的标准来算的话
well,
师哥
I suggest
我的建议
buying it
买下来
as it's more cost-effective.
更划算
Ji Yuheng,
纪昱恒
you're slicker than you're in school.
你比上学的时候滑头啊
In the end, you still come out on top.
那算来算去都是你赚
Fine,
行
see you at Dairui.
代瑞见
It's a deal.
您说的
C'mon,
来
let me see you out.
我送您出去
Take care.
慢走啊 师哥
Go.
走
Why
你刚才
did you suddenly...
怎么突然
Suddenly what?
突然什么
Just...
就突然
I'm drunk.
我喝醉了
You seem quite sober to me.
我看你清醒得很呀
You even know the loan standards,
还知道贷款额度标准
the auction standards,
和流拍标准
and how to make it
还知道怎么操作
more cost-effective for Dairui.
对代瑞来说更划算
Are you suggesting I planned them all?
不然难道是我计划好的
Helping Fanggang make connections
那帮小赵哥牵线搭桥
and deal with auctioned properties,
帮他处理流拍物
that was part of your plan, right?
总是你计划好的吧
I feel a bit tipsy
突然觉得吹了点风
from the breeze.
有点醉了
Let's go home.
我们回家
Are you kidding?
谁要跟你回家
Thanks to you,
拜纪总所赐
I have to drive them away.
我还要当司机呢
Has Mr. Jiang left?
姜总走了
Yes, Jing.
走了 姐
I noticed Mr. Ji drank quite a bit.
我看纪总也没少喝
You should take him home first.
你先送他回去吧
No need.
不用
He just said
纪总刚才说了
he wanna walk alone
想自己一个人走走
to sober up.
醒醒酒
I'll take you first.
我先送你们吧
Right, Mr. Ji?
是吧纪总
Why didn't you say you're leaving?
怎么走也不说一声
The room is empty now.
回去包房都空了
Where's Mr. Jiang?
姜总呢
He left.
走了
I'm leaving now.
我先走了
Let's go, Fanggang.
走吧小赵哥
Be safe.
注意安全啊
Let's go.
走
Take it slow.
慢点啊
Okay, thanks.
好 谢谢
Breathe quieter, will you?
你呼吸能不能小点声
I really don't get it.
我实在是不明白啊
What is Ji Yuheng
纪昱恒这小子
up to?
到底什么意思
A slap on the wrist and a candy?
给个巴掌赏个红枣
Sugar-coated bullets?
糖衣炮弹
Always saying
天天嘴上说着不共戴天
it's a fight to the death,
不共戴天
but I saw you
我看在那个酒桌上
cooperating well at the dinner table.
配合得挺好的
Work is work.
一码归一码
I can be professional.
这点专业性我还是有的
But
就是
what's his game
抵押物这事
with the collateral?
他到底什么意思
Always scheming
天天在办公室里边
and forming
拉帮结派
cliques in
跟人对着干
the office,
揣摩人的心思
but now
现在倒好
you can't
这点事
figure this out?
揣摩不明白了
By all accounts,
按理说
he should be at odds with me.
他应该膈应我呀
Why would he help me?
他为什么要帮我呢
Fanggang,
小赵哥
I think
我觉得吧
Mr. Ji wants to
纪总是想跟你
turn enemies into friends.
化敌为友
It's like
这
extending an olive branch.
就给你抛橄榄枝呢呀
Pardon?
化敌为友
If it's real,
他能跟我化敌为友
I would write my name backward.
我把名字倒着写
Even if he tries,
就算他跟我化敌为友
I'll still see him as an enemy.
我也跟他不共戴天
Here we go again.
又是不共戴天
You were always
之前在我这儿
badmouthing him
天天拉着我
to me,
跟我说人家坏话
and now after one kind gesture,
现在人给了你一个甜枣
you're just
你就分不清楚
so lost.
东南西北了
Can you speak properly?
你不会唠嗑别唠
I just helped you block some drinks.
亏我刚才还帮你挡酒
Do I need it?
我用你给我挡啊
With your drinking capacity?
就你那个酒量
Please...
你配吗
C'mon, what's that?
还哼
You plan
什么意思
to drop the feud
放下屠刀立地成佛
and make peace?
不跟我斗了
I've never had a grudge against you.
我没有跟你斗
We're in healthy competition.
我俩这就算良性竞争
No matter
而且我俩就是
how we compete,
就算是斗
it is
斗得再狠
still an
那也是我们一部
internal matter.
内部的事
Against
面对
outsiders,
外人
we should stand united.
我们要同仇敌忾
Stop that.
谁跟你俩你俩的
Letting you sit in the back
我让你坐后边
was me being nice.
都是给你面子
If you keep breathing loudly,
你要喘气再这么大声
sit in the front.
你给我上前边坐
Hi, Mr. Ji,
纪总
how's the hangover?
酒醒得怎么样
Didn't you say we're going separate ways?
不说各走各的吗
Get in the car.
上车
Let's go.
走吧
Well...
干吗呢
I made this for you.
这我给你准备的
Honey water, good for hangovers.
蜂蜜水配酒鬼
My experience tells me
我的经验告诉我
it works.
还是挺有用的
Drink it.
你快点喝
Why are you back?
怎么又回来了
I dropped them off at the subway
把他们送到地铁站
and thought
想着你一个人
it was too sad
孤苦伶仃的
to leave
太可怜了
you alone.
就回来接你呗
Plus,
再说
if a handsome man
万一我们
like you fell drunk
风华正茂的纪总
on the roadside
喝醉了倒在路边上
and caused some trouble,
被人劫财又劫色的
wouldn't that be a loss for me?
那我不是吃亏了
It is sweet.
还真是甜啊
But don't worry,
不过你可以放心
you know,
我呢
with family at home,
因为家里有人
I won't be
所以不可能
passing out outside.
醉倒在外面的
Mainly because
主要也是
you were good today,
你今天表现得好吗
trying to ease things with Fanggang.
主动跟小赵哥缓解关系
You showed
有那么一点点的
a bit of humanity.
人情味了
I couldn't
我实在是不忍心
leave you by the roadside.
把你一个人丢在路边
Sounds
听起来似乎
like a praise.
是在表扬我呢
Just words
那表扬我
for that?
只用嘴啊
Didn't I come back to pick you up?
我这不是回来接你了吗
What more do you want?
还要怎么样
You seem to be in a good mood.
看起来心情不错
How fancy bathing in the sea breeze
吃着冰激凌吹着海风
with ice cream
当然心情不错了
in hand!
多浪漫啊
Of course,
而且
you made me happy too.
你也让我很高兴
Tell me more.
展开来说说
You've resolved your issues
你跟小赵哥的问题
with Fanggang,
解决了
so I no longer
我以后就不用在
have to walk on eggshells
你们两个人之间
between you two.
如履薄冰了呀
Mr. Ji,
纪总
you've really improved a lot
你在我的教导下
under my guidance.
真的是进步不少
That's true.
这倒是
You admit that so quickly.
你怎么这么快就承认了
Because what you said
我觉得你说得
makes sense.
很有道理
I'm just an ordinary person
我也是一个普通人吗
with
身上也会有
various flaws
这样那样的缺点
and shortcomings.
也会有自己的不足
Actually, I'm quite happy
其实我还是很开心的
that you can
你能够
remind me of them
在我的生活里面
in my life.
去提醒我
It's really great that
你这样真的很好
you can change so quickly,
说改变就改变
follow through with your words,
言出必行
recognize your issues,
可以直视自己的问题
and also
也可以
correct them.
改正自己的问题
But I still need
不过还是要谢谢你
to thank you for guiding me.
谢谢你平时能够指点我
Should I
我是不是可以
become a life coach?
当人生导师去
Staying at Dairui is a waste.
我待在代瑞都屈才了
Why aren't you eating?
你怎么不吃
It's winter.
大冬天的
Don't you think it's too cold?
不会觉得很凉吗
Not at all.
不会啊
Winter is
大冬天的
the best time for ice cream.
才要吃冰激凌啊
It doesn't
这样不用担心
melt quickly,
冰激凌很快地化掉
so you can enjoy it slowly.
可以慢慢地享用
If you don't want it,
你要是不吃的话
give it to me.
给我吧
No.
不用
C'mon.
给我
I said no.
我说了不用
I'll eat it for you.
我替你吃
Why eat mine?
干吗吃我的
Yours tastes better.
你的好吃
Your mouth
吃得
is covered in it
满嘴都是
like a child.
像小孩
What are you doing?
干吗
The winter sea
冬天的海水
is cold.
有点凉
Put me down.
你快放我下来
The moonlight
今天的月色
is beautiful tonight.
很美
The sound of the waves is soothing,
海浪声很好听
and my heartbeat
心跳声
is loud.
也很大
This is against the rules.
这可是违规啊
Well...
这
Good morning.
早
Hi, Xiaoning.
小涂
These flowers aren't cheap.
这花可不便宜啊
Such a big bouquet, it's beautiful.
好大一把可漂亮了
Yeah.
是啊
Who sent them?
谁送的呀
Although you're in different depts,
虽然你们不同部门
flaunting
但是秀恩爱
your relationship
还是要有度
can make others jealous.
要不然容易招人嫉妒
What?
我们
Who are you referring to?
我跟谁呀
C'mon,
还能有谁啊
Qi Yu, of course.
齐郁呗
They're
这花
pretty.
挺漂亮的
Take care of them.
好好照顾
I drank too much last night.
我昨晚上喝太多
I still have a hangover.
现在头还疼
Fanggang!
小赵哥
Don't mismatch us.
乱点情侣
Who sent them?
谁送的呀
There's not even a note.
也不知道留一个卡片
Are those flowers from Ji Yuheng?
那个花是纪昱恒送的
Probably.
应该是纪昱恒送的
You kept complaining
前两天还因为
about him the other day
他不长嘴的事
'cause he didn't talk
说他眼睛不是眼睛
to people nicely.
鼻子不是鼻子的
Women are so unpredictable.
女人是真善变
Aren't you the same?
你不也一样
What about the other night?
我还没说你呢
After the party,
前两天聚会结束以后
did Qi Yu wait
齐郁是不是
at your doorstep all night?
在你家等了一晚上
How did you feel?
怎么样
Did it pull your heartstrings?
心里有没有起什么波澜
Qi Yu and Ji Yuheng
这齐郁跟纪昱恒啊
are not the same.
性质可不一样
For Ji Yuheng,
纪昱恒
his flaws
那微不足道的缺点
are like tiny ripples,
简直就是花拳绣腿
while Qi Yu's
齐郁给我带来的
huge wave
大风大浪
almost capsized
可是差点掀翻了
the boat of my life.
我人生的小船
You don't share
你们俩虽然没什么
any common memories
美好的过去
from the past,
可也没有什么
good or bad.
糟糕的过去
Unlike us...
不像我们俩
Alright.
算了
There's no point in talking about it.
不说了没意义
Well,
好了 好了
stop being upset.
别不高兴了
You have me by your side.
不还有我呢吗
We have a great past,
咱们俩有美好的过去
and also a better future.
更有美好的未来
You can always
我的胸膛
lay on my chest.
永远为你敞开
Up yours.
去你的
I just want
谁要你的胸膛
the chest of cool boys.
我要帅哥的胸膛
Okay, Mr. Shen.
行啊沈总
I'll wait until
就看您什么时候
you're free.
有时间吧
Okay.
行
We'll talk later.
那咱回头再联系
What's about the smile?
想什么呢笑这么甜
Nothing.
没想什么
Do you want something?
静姐你找我有事啊
Get your stuff.
收拾一下
Come with me to Renji Hospital.
陪我去一趟仁济医院
Okay.
好
In a minute.
我马上
Hurry up.
快点啊
Do you know the process of
办理代发工资卡的流程
starting payroll service?
都清楚吧
Yes. I've just learned.
清楚 我刚学过
That's not hard.
那个是不难
The hard part is to recommend
难的是办卡之后
our financial products
顺带向医生推荐
and credit cards.
我行的理财还有信用卡
I'll do all of them?
信用卡和理财也给我做
Can you?
办不了啊
Yes!
能
I'll do my best.
我一定好好做
You took me into
就是我之前不是
business before,
请姐带着我做业务吗
but you said
您不是说
I wasn't good enough.
不到时候吗
You've made some progress
我看你最近业务上
in your business lately.
有点进步
It's about time
也是时候
you practiced.
该接触一下实务了
Besides, the process of
再说了办工资卡
payroll service is trivial.
是一个琐碎的事情
I can't do it all by myself.
我一个人忙不过来
I'll go up and
我先上去跟
have a word with the CFO.
跟财务主任说几句话
You go straight to the sixth floor.
你直接去六楼
They keep an office
他们在那儿给我们
for us there.
留了一个办公室
Start the payroll service first.
先帮大家办卡
Okay.
好
I don't think
我觉得啊
it's from
就不是那个
the driver
叫什么齐郁的
named Qi Yu.
那司机送的
He looks too dull.
你看他呆头呆脑的样
Fanggang.
赵哥
What do you say?
你觉得呢
There's
每一张
a romantic soul
憨厚质朴的外表下
underneath the rustic appearance.
都住着一颗浪漫的灵魂
Do you understand "romantic"?
罗曼蒂克你知道吗
Well,
那可真是
I'm sorry for Xiaoning.
可惜咱们小涂了
She deserves
怎么着得找个
a better man.
条件更好一点的
Yes.
是
The registration is almost finished.
工资卡登记得差不多了
May I have
不好意思
your attention please?
打扰一下各位啊
Please have a look
麻烦大家看一下
at the brochure about credit card.
手里的信用卡宣传单
It's an add-on
因为是工资卡
service to the payroll card.
跟信用卡联办
All doctors and nurses
所以只要是
at this hospital
咱们医院的医生
who apply for this
或者是护士申请
can enjoy a limit
额度可以达到
of over 50,000 yuan.
五万块钱以上
You can use the payroll card
如果开通的话每个月
to pay off the credit card
可以用自己的工资卡
directly every month
直接还信用卡
without any fee.
就免手续费的
It's a good deal.
也是很划算
That's convenient.
这倒是挺方便的
But I don't think another card
但总觉得再办一张的话
is necessary.
没什么太大必要
He's right.
对呀
How about
要不
you just register?
先登记
You can get a trolley case
今天登记的话
and supermarket membership
会有免费的拉杆箱
for today.
还有超市会员赠送
A trolley case?
还有拉杆箱
And supermarket membership?
超市会员啊
I need one.
我办一张
Sijing.
思靖
Didn't realize
你这条件
you could need a credit card.
还用得着办信用卡啊
Of course I need it.
当然了
There's a lot of bills.
花钱地方多着呢
How about you?
你也办一张啊
But...
我刚想了想
I don't think
算了吧
it's of use.
用不上
C'mon. It's of great use.
怎么会用不上啊
It can help you get a discount
代瑞银行的信用卡
on dinner on Wednesdays
周三吃饭打折
and double points to redeem
周五双倍积分
movie tickets on Fridays.
兑换电影票
You can save your boyfriend money on dates.
约会多帮你男朋友省钱
Stop making fun of me.
你这人真是
How do you know it so much?
你怎么知道得这么清楚
Didn't you just come back from abroad?
你不是刚从国外回来吗
Stop asking.
就你的问题多
Start registering.
你也得办啊
C'mon, everybody!
来大家都办
Xiaoning.
筱柠
I can get
说的是
a free trolley case, right?
免费送拉杆箱
Yes.
是 是 是
Here.
来 来 来
Jing.
静姐
Where's your work permit?
工作证呢
Here.
这呢
Remember to wear it
下次办业务的时候
when doing business.
专业一点戴上
How's it going?
进展得怎么样了
I almost finished the
工资卡登记得
payroll service registration.
都差不多了
But I don't think
信用卡
they're interested in credit cards.
大家好像都不太感兴趣
I saw that doctor
我刚才看那个医生
warming up to you.
好像对你挺热情
Any stories about you two?
追求者啊
Um...
不是
Your ex?
前男友
Look at this.
来大家都看看这个
Here.
来 来 来
Take it.
给
It's actually a business
信用卡业务呢
that every bank is striving for.
是每个银行抢占的市场
He's popular.
我看他人缘不错
People love to listen to him.
号召力也挺强的
Make good use of it.
物尽其用吧
Jing.
静姐
I don't want too much
我不想跟他
contact with him.
有过多的接触
I don't want his help with my work.
也不想挣他的钱
You're just doing your job.
挣钱还分
Every help counts.
你的他的
It's just a small favor
他帮你办卡
from him.
只是捎带手的事
If they didn't get credit cards today,
今天他不在咱们银行办
other banks would take
改天这个业务
the chance away from us tomorrow.
也会被其他银行收割的
You do marketing.
所以我们干营销的呢
You need to open your mind
就是要把思路打开
to all possible resources
发掘身边一切
around you.
可能性的资源
So, none
所以不管
of his identities should be
他是你的前男友
an obstacle to you.
还是现男友
Potential resource is everything.
挖掘资源最重要
If less than 10 cards today,
今天拿不下十张卡
you don't come back.
别回来见我
Is everyone clear on this?
大家了解得怎么样了
Actually,
其实
Sijing is my friend from college.
思靖是我的大学同学
And you're coworkers.
你们又是同事
I'll try to give you a better deal
那今天咱们申请
if you apply for one today.
一定会得到更多的优惠
You're friends.
原来是同学啊
They're in.
他们都办啊
Here.
来 来 来
Look at it.
都看看
He knows her.
知根知底
Yeah.
对知根知底的
You can count on me.
大家放心
Here.
来
Look at it.
大家看一下这个
Thank you.
谢谢啊
You didn't answer my calls
这些天我跟你联系
these days.
你也不接电话
I thought you...
我还以为你
Well,
那个
how's the flowers?
花还喜欢吗
You sent them?
花是你送的
Why are you surprised?
应该是谁送的
You're back.
回来了
Just in time.
来得早不如来得巧
Are you tired?
累坏了吧
What's that good smell?
什么这么香啊
Chef Ji.
纪师傅
You're great!
厉害呀
Of course.
那是
Good?
还不错
Wonderful!
不错
You're a good cook.
纪师傅好手艺
Here.
来
Arms up.
把手抬起来
I heard from Zhao Fanggang that you
我听赵方刚说
went to the hospital with Rao Jing.
你跟饶静去了趟医院
How's everything going?
都还顺利吗
It went well.
挺顺利的
After all,
再怎么说
I've been a lobby manager
我也是做了
for a few years.
几年大堂经理的人
It's just a credit card promotion.
推销信用卡而已
It did start out a little rough.
一开始呢确实有些不利
But later
后来呢
it's okay.
就很顺利了
Delicious.
好吃
Make more.
再烤点
Try this.
尝尝这个
What's going on today?
你怎么回事啊
You must want something from me.
你想说什么你就说呗
We're at home.
怎么在家里
Just say it.
还吞吞吐吐的
Did you
你今天
get flowers today?
是不是收到花了呀
Never mind.
没什么
Help yourself.
趁热吃吧
Our school is pretty big.
我们学校挺大的
It's easy to get lost on your first visit.
第一次来确实容易迷路
Why don't you
同学
have your girlfriend
怎么没找女朋友
pick you up?
来接你啊
She's not my girlfriend.
不是女朋友
So, she doesn't know how you feel yet.
原来是心上人啊
You're here to confess?
来表白的
It's her birthday.
今天她生日
The girls' dorm is right there.
女生宿舍就在那儿呢
Good luck.
祝你成功
Xiaoning.
筱柠
Happy birthday.
生日快乐
I don't know...
我也不知道你喜欢
what color roses you like,
什么颜色的玫瑰花
so I've got these.
所以我都准备了一点
Check it.
你 你看看
Do you like any of them?
有你喜欢的吗
I like this.
我喜欢这个
I'll remember.
我记住了
Xiaoning, I…
筱柠 我
I love you!
筱柠我喜欢你
I want to buy you
我想为你买遍
every blue rose in the world.
世上所有蓝色的玫瑰花
I hope you can
希望你可以
be my girlfriend.
给我这个机会
Say yes! Say yes!
答应他 答应他
Give here a hug!
抱一个 抱一个
Kiss her!
亲一个
Kiss her! Kiss her!
亲一个 亲一个
What's wrong with me today?
我今天是怎么了
I should have made it clear
就应该清楚地说
that I thought they're from him.
我以为是他送的
It wouldn't have been so awkward.
就不会弄得这么尴尬了
I need to tell him about
陆思靖的事儿
Lu Sijing as soon as possible.
我要尽快说明白
I can't
不能再让
let this happen again.
这样的事情发生
Xiaoning.
小涂
Why did you throw away
怎么把昨天给你送的花
the flowers?
扔了呢
Did you have a quarrel?
吵架了
No.
没有
Did he mistreat you?
是不是欺负你了
You tell me.
你跟哥说
I'll kick his ass.
哥教训教训他
No, Fanggang.
没有小赵哥
What are you talking about?
聊什么呢
Just small talk between coworkers.
同事之间聊聊天
It's nothing to do with you.
聊不到你纪总头上来
Follow me.
来会议室一趟
You don't need my introduction.
不用我多介绍了吧
The guarantor
你那笔
of the bad loan you're
不良贷款的担保人
responsible for.
沈总
Nice to meet you.
久仰 久仰
I haven't had the chance
约了您好几次都没约上
to meet you.
今天总算能见到了
You don't have to
你们就不用
beat around the bush.
跟我兜圈子了
Mr. Ji.
纪总
Just cut to the chase.
直入主题吧
Okay.
好
Since your account manager
既然您的管户经理
has arrived,
已经到了
I'll get right to the point.
那我也开门见山
The foreclosure sale is imminent.
法院拍卖抵押物在即
I'm calling on you
这次喊您过来
to do us a favor
就是希望您能够
to prevent the security
帮我们一个忙
from being unsold.
不让这个抵押物流拍
What do you mean?
什么意思
You don't have to do anything
您什么都不用做
but participate in
只要参与
the auction.
这次的竞拍就好
Mr. Ji.
纪总
Mr. Zhao.
赵经理
Are you here to help me
你们是来帮我
solve my problems
解决问题的
or to create some more?
还是来制造问题的
Mr. Shen.
沈总
Don't get upset.
您消消气
We're helping you avoid a lawsuit.
我们是怕您打官司
Think about it.
您看
Usually, a lawsuit ends up
多少案例判下来
with the guarantor
最终还是担保人
paying all the money.
一分不少地赔钱
Just as Mr. Ji said,
纪总刚才也说到了
you can lose less
您参加竞拍
if you
赔得
bid on.
会更少
Lawsuits are time-consuming
而且打官司
and laborious.
耗时又费劲
We're
咱们两方
on the same side now.
现在是一条船上的蚂蚱
Mr. Shen.
沈总
You must be here
今天既然您
'cause
能来代瑞
you trust us.
就说明对我们是信任的
Please.
希望您能相信我们
Let's work this out
让我们一起
together.
来解决这个问题
So, tell me exactly
那你们说说
what I need to do.
具体需要我怎么配合
Mr. Shen.
沈总
Call me if you
您这边有任何疑问
have any questions.
随时打我电话
I'm online 24/7.
我二十四小时在线
I will.
尽快吧
Thank you.
辛苦
See you soon.
拜拜
Why do you help me?
为什么帮我
It's not just for you,
也不只是帮你
but more for the department.
更多的是为了这个部门
I'm counting on you
沈总那边就辛苦你了
for his business.
多跟进一下
Don't worry.
你放心吧
I'll take care of everything
沈总和姜总那边
about Mr. Shen and Mr. Jiang.
我都会好好对接的
Mr. Ji.
纪总
Thank you.
谢谢
Go back to work.
上班吧
When did I
我什么时候
become so shy?
变得这么扭捏了
Yikes!
肉麻
Actually, Mr. Ji
其实我们纪总
isn't a bad person.
人真的不坏
He's
可能
just need an improvement
性格上确实有一丢丢的
on the character.
进步空间
After all, he's been abroad
但他毕竟一个人在国外
alone for so long.
深造求学了那么久
It's common
那不太会
for him not to be good at
表达自己的感情
expressing his feelings.
也是很正常的
This time,
这回呢
he helped Fanggang out.
拉了小赵哥一把
It's also a perfect
也完全体现了
example that
纪总的
he's a responsible man.
责任 担当
Oh my goodness.
你听听 你听听
There's a pride
这话里话外
in every word of yours.
自豪骄傲的劲
Looks like
这预备役老婆
you're definitely
看来当的是
gonna marry him.
挺得心应手的呀
Can you survive a whole year
还熬得住一年之后
to become Mrs. Ji?
才转正为纪太太吗
It's not
熬不熬得住
up to me.
也不是我说了算
We had a deal
我们俩决定
and set our
开始这段关系之前
own KPI
就说好了
before we started
也自己给自己定了
this relationship.
关键绩效指标
Whoever doesn't finish it
谁没完成
will leave.
谁走人
I have to say,
不得不说
you two are real
你俩是真正的
professionals.
职业男女啊
What? KPI?
还关键绩效指标
So how are you doing
那你这关键绩效指标
on yours?
完成得怎么样了
To turn to permanent,
为了转正
I've made Lu Sijing
我把陆思靖
my client.
都发展成客户了
I work all day long
白天披星戴月地工作
and prepare for
晚上回去
the test at night.
还要准备考试的东西
And you still have time
那你还有时间
for a facial massage with me.
陪我出来做脸
I knew
我就知道
you love me so much.
我们肯定是真爱了
Of course.
那当然了
You've called me 3 times this week.
你这一星期找了我三次
Spit it out.
快说
What do you want?
怎么回事
I want to hide away.
避难
What's going on?
怎么了
I'm not hiding from anyone else,
我要躲的不是别人
but Qi Yu.
是齐郁
You don't know
你是不知道
how many stupid things he's done
他这段时间为了追我
to pursue me.
干了多少蠢事
I'm all ears.
说来听听
I posted a Moment
周三我不是
on Wednesday
发了个朋友圈吗
saying that I didn't get a ticket
说我那演唱会的门票
to the concert.
没抢到
He took three different buses
他倒了三趟公交车
to the outskirts for a
去市郊给我买了一张
scalped ticket.
黄牛票
I knew it's fake on sight.
结果一眼假
This is not the end.
这还不是最绝的
You know,
最绝的
I left a pair of old shoes on the doorstep,
我放了双鞋放在门口
ready to be discarded.
很明显是不要了
But he
他好
fixed the break with glue
跑去买个五零二
and brought them back to me.
帮我粘上给我拿回来
Isn't it annoying?
你说气不气人
I think it's sweet.
听着还挺感人的
Qi Yu's love for you
齐郁对你的爱呢
is simple
属于那种简单质朴
yet profound.
深刻的爱
Late love is the cheapest.
迟来的深情比草贱
I don't give a damn.
我才不稀罕呢
Where are you?
在哪儿呢
I just finished extra work.
我刚刚加班结束
I'm gonna pick you up.
现在过去接你
It's too much work for you.
太麻烦了吧
No.
不会啊
I wanna
我去接你
go home with you together.
咱们一块回家
Okay.
好吧
I'm at the spa.
我在水疗馆
Right.
好
I'll see you later.
那一会儿见
How comfortable!
真舒服
Watching others
这恋爱
fall in love is more interesting.
还是看别人谈有意思
You haven't seen for just hours.
这才多久没见
Isn't it too much?
太夸张了吧
Look at you.
这 这 这
I can almost see the lust
小眼神噼里啪啦地
in your eyes.
都快冒火星子了
Don't exaggerate.
别噼里啪啦的
Cut it out.
少说点
Are you tired?
累不累啊
C'mon, we laid there
在那儿躺了
for two hours.
两个小时怎么累
Mr. Ji.
纪总
What are you doing here?
您怎么在这儿
Did you get the file
我刚才给你的文件
I just gave you?
您收好了吧
I'm sorry.
不好意思啊
I won't take any papers
我下次一定注意
home anymore.
不把文件带回家
We've got work to do.
那我们俩还有事
We gotta go.
我先走了啊
Xiaoning,
筱柠
wait a minute.
你等一下
Sijing has something important to tell you.
思靖有重要的事和你讲
My work is really important.
我真的有很重要的事情
Let's talk about it some other time.
改天再说吧
Xiaoning!
筱柠
Only a barbecue
今日份上班的烦恼
could cure
只有一顿烤肉
my workday woes.
才能疗愈
How could you know
你怎么知道
I wanted a barbecue today?
我今天想吃烤肉
I know everything.
我一直都知道